<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dietica</string>
    <string name="subHeadingText">
        Let’s start a healthier life one scan at a time. Understand your meals, plan your habits, and manage your activity in one click!
    </string>
    <string name="general_information_text">
        Let us know your name! Don’t forget your password!
    </string>

    <string-array name="gender_options">
        <item>Select Gender</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_level_options">
        <item>Select Activity Levels</item>
        <item>Sedentary</item>
        <item>Light Activity</item>
        <item>Active</item>
        <item>Heavy Active</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="default_web_client_id">
        253336274684-2u4c7u979beoo64cca707lsnpb2pq0ta.apps.googleusercontent.com
    </string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText">Welcome to Dietica, a health app designed to support you in achieving your personal health and wellness goals. By using Dietica, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions. Please read them carefully.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText2">By downloading, accessing, or using Dietica, you agree to these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree, you must not use the App.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText4">Dietica is a health and wellness app that uses generative AI technology to provide personalized suggestions, tips, and resources for users to help achieve health and fitness goals. The App’s content is intended for informational purposes only and should not replace professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText6">Dietica is intended for individuals aged 18 and over. If you are under 18, you must have permission from a parent or guardian to use the App.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText8">Not Medical Advice: Dietica does not provide medical or clinical advice. The content and suggestions are based on general health principles and user-provided information. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before making changes to your diet, exercise, or wellness routine.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText12">Limitations: The generative AI suggestions provided by Dietica are based on algorithms analyzing user inputs and available health data. AI-generated suggestions may not be perfect or applicable to all users. Personalization: Dietica uses AI to tailor suggestions to your goals and preferences; however, results may vary based on individual responses, and you are encouraged to monitor and adjust based on personal experience.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText">Dietica is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share, and safeguard your personal information when you use our health and wellness app, Dietica. By using Dietica, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText2">To provide personalized recommendations and improve your experience, Dietica collects the following types of information: a. Personal Information We may collect personally identifiable information, such as your: Name Email address Age Height, weight, and other health metrics b. Health and Fitness Information When you use Dietica, you may provide health and fitness-related information, such as: Diet preferences Exercise habits Weight loss or fitness goals Medical history (if relevant and voluntarily provided) c. Device and Usage Information We may automatically collect certain information when you access or use the App, including: Device information (e.g., device type, operating system) IP address Usage data (e.g., features used, time spent on the App) App activity logs and interaction patterns d. Location Information With your consent, we may collect approximate location data to personalize recommendations based on your location.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText4">Dietica uses the information we collect for the following purposes: Personalization: To tailor the App’s suggestions and content to meet your health and wellness goals. Health Recommendations: To provide generative AI-driven health, fitness, and dietary recommendations. Customer Support: To respond to your inquiries, troubleshoot issues, and improve your experience. App Improvement: To analyze user behavior and feedback to enhance our App’s functionality, content, and design. Compliance and Legal Obligations: To comply with applicable laws, regulations, and protect our legal rights.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText6">Dietica does not sell your personal information to third parties. We may share your information in the following situations: Service Providers: We may engage third-party vendors to provide services on our behalf (e.g., cloud storage, analytics) with access only to information necessary to perform their tasks. Legal Requirements: We may disclose your information if required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, legal process, or government request. Business Transfers: If Dietica undergoes a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText14">Your privacy is important to us. Please review our Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, and safeguard your information.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText16">You agree not to: Use the App for unlawful or prohibited activities. Provide false, misleading, or inaccurate information. Access or attempt to access the accounts of other users or violate their privacy.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText18">All content provided by Dietica, including but not limited to text, images, and software, is the property of Dietica or its licensors and is protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws. You may not copy, distribute, or reproduce any part of the App without express permission.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText20">License: Dietica grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to use the App solely for personal, non-commercial purposes. Restrictions: You may not modify, reverse-engineer, or attempt to extract the source code of the App.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText22">Dietica may contain links to third-party websites, products, or services. These links are provided for convenience, and Dietica does not endorse or assume responsibility for any third-party content or practices.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText24">Dietica is provided on an as-is and as-available basis. Dietica makes no warranties, expressed or implied, regarding the App’s performance, reliability, or accuracy. We do not guarantee that the App will be error-free, secure, or free from interruptions.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText26">To the maximum extent permitted by law, Dietica and its affiliates, employees, and partners shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, including but not limited to loss of data, revenue, or health outcomes.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText28">You agree to indemnify and hold harmless Dietica, its affiliates, employees, and partners from any claims, liabilities, damages, and expenses (including legal fees) arising from your use of the App or violation of these Terms.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText30">Dietica reserves the right to suspend or terminate your access to the App at any time, with or without notice, for conduct that violates these Terms or is harmful to other users.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText32">We may update these Terms periodically. If we make significant changes, we will notify you through the App or via email. Continued use of the App after such updates constitutes acceptance of the new Terms.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText34">These Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of [Country/State].</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionText36">If you have any questions or concerns about these Terms, please contact us at [support@dietica.com].</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText8">We implement a variety of security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. However, no internet-based application can guarantee complete security. By using the App, you acknowledge that you understand and accept these risks.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText10">Depending on your jurisdiction, you may have the following rights regarding your personal information: Access: You may request access to the personal information we hold about you. Correction: You have the right to request correction of any inaccurate or incomplete information. Deletion: You may request that we delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions. Restriction of Processing: You may request that we limit the processing of your personal information in certain cases. Data Portability: You may have the right to receive a copy of your personal information in a commonly used format.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText12">We retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required by law.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText14">Dietica is not intended for use by individuals under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If we learn that we have collected information from a child under 18 without parental consent, we will delete it.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText16">Dietica may contain links to third-party websites or services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties, and we encourage you to review their privacy policies before providing any personal information.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText19">We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices, legal requirements, or other factors. When we make significant changes, we will notify you through the App or via email. Your continued use of Dietica after such updates constitutes acceptance of the new Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicyText21">If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or our data practices, please contact us at: Email: privacy@dietica.com</string>


</resources>